<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-06-14T11:58:06-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The Civilized Chimp</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2016/06/13/the-civilized-chimp.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Civilized Chimp" /><published>2016-06-13T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2016-06-13T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2016/06/13/the-civilized-chimp</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2016/06/13/the-civilized-chimp.html">&lt;p&gt;It all started with a spark that gave birth to humanity, the moment the universe would begin to bend to our will. We were just simple creatures with sharp sticks and a want for more. As a result we formed small groups and although weak alone, we stood strong in numbers. We elected wise kings to lead our newly born nations and crafted flags adorned with the symbols of our ideologies and organizations. We forged sharp sticks that evolved into deadly blades to slay our enemies to gain fame and with each continent conquered it added to the melting pot which was our culture. Monuments stood long after our civilization’s vanish as a reminder of a golden era that crumbled to the dusts of time. Nations are born out of the ashes of these fallen nations heralding the rise of a more modern era.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blades and cavalry soon transformed into guns and armored vehicles, war machines that screamed and whistled across the battlefield. It was a race to see who had the biggest stick and before we knew it we had the power to destroy each other with the push of a button. The global fear of nuclear death raining down on our heads rendered the classic eras of war unprofitable and dead thus spawning an age of peace and prosperity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a never ending tug of war between us and our curiosity for the unknown. The weapons we once used to destroy one another now allow us to reach beyond the glassy skies and into the event horizon. With each generation’s pass we built upon each other mistakes forming new ideas and theories about our ever expanding universe. With our rapid growth in the recent years coupled with our short temper its amazing that we haven’t completely annihilated each other. Touching the cosmos we’re right back where we started, just a curious ape with a lust for more power.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It all started with a spark that gave birth to humanity, the moment the universe would begin to bend to our will. We were just simple creatures with sharp sticks and a want for more. As a result we formed small groups and although weak alone, we stood strong in numbers. We elected wise kings to lead our newly born nations and crafted flags adorned with the symbols of our ideologies and organizations. We forged sharp sticks that evolved into deadly blades to slay our enemies to gain fame and with each continent conquered it added to the melting pot which was our culture. Monuments stood long after our civilization’s vanish as a reminder of a golden era that crumbled to the dusts of time. Nations are born out of the ashes of these fallen nations heralding the rise of a more modern era.</summary></entry></feed>