<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-06-14T22:40:18-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The Stairway To Infinity</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/14/the-stairway-to-infinity.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Stairway To Infinity" /><published>2019-06-14T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-14T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/14/the-stairway-to-infinity</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/14/the-stairway-to-infinity.html">&lt;p&gt;Pitch black darkness. I would imagine this was our life before birth, suspended in nothingness and truly at peace. Our modern lives contrast these early beginnings however as even the world we call home was forged in a fiery nest nurtured by chaos. Most of us are born to struggle in the mud lands of our own problems and not many find their escape. Countless get devoured by their demons and those who survive either come out the other side broken or rise to become immortals. This eternal fight is what fueled our species to adapt and achieve greatness beyond comprehension. It’s a lifetime of mistakes that have contributed to the success of humanity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The journey is long and we often find ourselves lost in the cruel sea of thought, crafting problems in our head before they have the chance to attack. The overwhelming burdens of life force us to look back at the simpler times when the world seemed open and new. We find innocent babies so adorable as they fumble about trying to exist, I wonder if the gods look down upon us thinking the same thing as we try to understand the complex threads that make up the fabric of reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, we all have potential, like a blank canvas we can all grow into a masterpiece. We humans possess a tool that can mold this world into anything. Never in the history of mankind have we had the power to access knowledge so freely and almost instantaneously. The ability to be everywhere and having a voice that echos the globe would be considered magic a few centuries ago. It makes you wonder what this world will look like in the next hundred years. Will it be a paradise or a technological nightmare? Whatever the outcome lets enjoy this blue rock together.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Pitch black darkness. I would imagine this was our life before birth, suspended in nothingness and truly at peace. Our modern lives contrast these early beginnings however as even the world we call home was forged in a fiery nest nurtured by chaos. Most of us are born to struggle in the mud lands of our own problems and not many find their escape. Countless get devoured by their demons and those who survive either come out the other side broken or rise to become immortals. This eternal fight is what fueled our species to adapt and achieve greatness beyond comprehension. It’s a lifetime of mistakes that have contributed to the success of humanity.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Civilized Chimp</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/13/the-civilized-chimp.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Civilized Chimp" /><published>2019-06-13T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-13T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/13/the-civilized-chimp</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/13/the-civilized-chimp.html">&lt;p&gt;It all started with a spark that gave birth to humanity, the moment the universe would begin to bend to our will. We were just simple creatures with sharp sticks and a want for more. As a result we formed small groups and although weak alone, we stood strong in numbers. We elected wise kings to lead our newly born nations and crafted flags adorned with the symbols of our ideologies and organizations. We forged sharp sticks that evolved into deadly blades to slay our enemies to gain fame and with each continent conquered it added to the melting pot which was our culture. Monuments stood long after our civilization’s vanish as a reminder of a golden era that crumbled to the dusts of time. Nations are born out of the ashes of these fallen nations heralding the rise of a more modern era.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blades and cavalry soon transformed into guns and armored vehicles, war machines that screamed and whistled across the battlefield. It was a race to see who had the biggest stick and before we knew it we had the power to destroy each other with the push of a button. The global fear of nuclear death raining down on our heads rendered the classic eras of war unprofitable and dead thus spawning an age of peace and prosperity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a never ending tug of war between us and our curiosity for the unknown. The weapons we once used to destroy one another now allow us to reach beyond the glassy skies and into the event horizon. With each generation’s pass we built upon each other mistakes forming new ideas and theories about our ever expanding universe. With our rapid growth in the recent years coupled with our short temper its amazing that we haven’t completely annihilated each other. Touching the cosmos we’re right back where we started, just a curious ape with a lust for more power.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It all started with a spark that gave birth to humanity, the moment the universe would begin to bend to our will. We were just simple creatures with sharp sticks and a want for more. As a result we formed small groups and although weak alone, we stood strong in numbers. We elected wise kings to lead our newly born nations and crafted flags adorned with the symbols of our ideologies and organizations. We forged sharp sticks that evolved into deadly blades to slay our enemies to gain fame and with each continent conquered it added to the melting pot which was our culture. Monuments stood long after our civilization’s vanish as a reminder of a golden era that crumbled to the dusts of time. Nations are born out of the ashes of these fallen nations heralding the rise of a more modern era.</summary></entry></feed>